Dive deep into serious learning,
and get excited!
Witness a miracle born from fossils.
Once upon a time, in a certain place...
Prehistoric creatures full of personality!
Tirano, Stego, Ammonite,Trilobite.
They've been saying "hi" for 500 million years.
Prehistory! Everybody Say (Roar!)
Ancient, Alright! Future, FLY High!
A herd of mammoths! Run!
Thud thud thud thud! On your marks, get set, go!
Dive deep into serious learning,
and get excited!
Witness a miracle born from fossils.
Dive deep into serious learning,
Playing for real.
The universe begins with passion.
Super happy!
What is this person?
Serious Spinosaurus Quiz
Person?
You...
How long have you been there?
No, "that" part.
Please let me join the club!
Huh? You want to join?
Welcome to the Paleontology Research Club!
Your attitude changed way too fast!
What is your name?
I'm Dino.
That's an unusual name...
Alright, hand in your application right away!
Understood.
I refuse!
Why are you accepting it if you're going to decline?!
Please test me to see if I'm qualified to join!
Interesting!
Then welcome to the world of SERIOUS PALEONTOLOGY!
Why am I dragged into this too?!
EXPLOSION! Prehistoric Silhouette Quiz!
Dino or whatever your name is!
If you get even one question right, I'll accept you!
I decline!
Make the condition that I must answer ALL questions correctly!
Why are you raising the bar for yourself?!
Question 1!
What prehistoric creature's bone is this?
Hmph, don't underestimate me!
These conical teeth and elongated snout adapted for aquatic hunting...
Whoa!
Impressive!
Which means the answer is...
a Crocodile!
WRONG! This is the skull of a Spinosaurus!
Spino...?
It seems he didn't actually know at all...
It is a theropod dinosaur said to have reached up to 15 meters in length!
I failed.
Please give me the next question!
EH?
Alright!
Question 2!
What prehistoric creature's bone is this?
I won't make the same mistake twice!
This fin-like structure called a neural spine...
The creature with such bones is...
The creature with such bones is?
The American Bison!
We're talking about PREHISTORIC creatures!
This is the neural spine from a Spinosaurus's sail!
However, the exact reason why it had a sail is still unknown to this day!
Huh?
Isn't that different from the previous picture?
Jumping Chance!
If you get the final question right, you become Vice President!
EH?
Well, there are no other members anyway...
Did Spinosaurus...
walk on two legs?
or four legs?
Which one is it?!
This is the last one, I can't miss it!
The answer is...
IT'S FOUR LEGS!
BOTH ARE CORRECT!
Wait, that feels kinda cheap!
It's not cheap at all!
Two or four legs...
Whether it walked on two or four legs is a debate still actively ongoing with every new discovery and research!
Furthermore,
because complete fossils are rarely found,
scholars have long debated whether its back had a single hump or a double hump!
Why is there such a debate?
Because Spinosaurus is...
a tragic prehistoric creature.
The museum housing its original fossils was destroyed in an airstrike,
causing the initial specimens to vanish forever.
However,
researchers never gave up despite that tragedy,
and continue to burn with passion!
Paleontology is a discipline filled
with indomitable fighting spirit!
Indomitable fighting spirit...
Welcome
to our Paleontology Research Club!
Mr. President...
I refuse!
WHAT?!
Why does it always end like this?!
Until I can answer every question correctly,
I will keep trying with an indomitable fighting spirit!
Eek!